Ian Littke

☐ (206) 659-6106 • ☐ ian.littke@gmail.com • ☐ github/mowzie • in linkedin/in/littke

Summary

Recent computer science graduate with experience in software development and testing with **C**, **C**# and **Java**. I am a quick learner that can easily adapt.

Languages and Technologies

Languages	C	C#	Java	Python	SQL
Technologies	git	Scikit-Learn	Tensorflow	WPF	
Elective Courses	Deep Learning	Device Drivers	Parallel Computation	Natural Language Processing	

Work Experience

POPULUS GROUP, LLC for MICROSOFT

Redmond, WA

2010–2015

Software Test Engineer

Software and hardware test engineer for Xbox

- Collected microphone/speaker data for statistical analysis on
- Rewrote existing test infrastructure from batch script to \mathbf{C} # reducing runtime by 50% while increasing received test data
- Created .NET webpage with graphs to show detailed information on automated tests
- Created tools for daily accuracy testing including Cortana/Xbox keyword spotter

Other

Audio Recordist

WESTERN WASHINGTON UNIVERSITY

Bellingham, WA

2016–2017

- Archival recording and digitizing analog recordings for the music department.

Projects of Interest

Western Washington University

Reinforcement Learning Project

2017

- Group project to use machine learning models to teach a rigid-body simulation in Unity
- Utilized ml-agents framework to tie Unity and **tensorflow**

WESTERN WASHINGTON UNIVERSITY

Flight Planner

2017

- Group project for the Whatcom Civil Air Patrol (CAP), written in C#
- Allows CAP to easily create Garmin G1000 navigation files
- Provided the majority of the front-end development
- Project information is stored at github.com/CIOS-Digital

EDMONDS COMMUNITY COLLEGE

Emergency Vehicle Detection: Frequency Detection and Localization

2015

- Experimental project (github.com/mowzie/vehiclefinder)
- Implemented a cross-correlation algorithm in **C** to determine frequencies of interest

Microsoft

Recording Tool

2013-2015

- Designed, developed, documented, and maintained in-house C# recording tool
- Interfaces with Xbox 360, Xbox One, Win10 devices, and a LUA-controlled gantry robot

Education

Western Washington UniversityBellingham, WABachelors of Science: Computer Science, GPA 3.332015–Dec 2017

Edmonds Community College

Associate of Science: Mathematics, GPA 3.75

Lynnwood, WA 2014–2015

Art Institute of SeattleSeattle, WAAssociate of Applied Arts: Audio Production, GPA 3.02007–2009